[Music]
hey guys it's Chloe and in today's
tutorial I want to share with you how to
get this loose textured effortless
french braid so if you want to learn how
to get this look then keep on watching
I'm starting off with freshly washed and
blow-dried hair and I'm taking the Aveda
texture tonic and spraying that from the
middle of my hair to the ends you can
apply this product on both damp and dry
hair to create a PC tousled texture next
I'm taking a large barreled curling wand
and curling large sections of my hair to
create natural waves
I love applying the texture tonic right
before curling my hair because it helps
my hair hold the curls all day and night
and it gives my curls more of a toss old
effortless look plus it will help my
hair hold the shape of the French braid
as well once all your hair is curled
it's time to start on the braid to get a
simple French braid just start by
creating a normal three-strand braid up
towards the crown of your head divide
the hair in three equal sections and
begin crossing the left side over the
middle section and then the right side
over the middle section keep doing this
and start adding more pieces of hair to
each section as you continue going down
the braid
and when you get to the nape of your
neck and run out of hair to add then
continue by braiding your hair normally
and secure the end with an elastic now
to get that effortless look start
pulling the braid piece by piece to get
more volume I also like to remove the
hair that frames my face from the braid
and quickly curly the more messy you
make your hair the more effortless the
braid looks and that's it you can find
any of the hair products I used online
at Aveda comm or at any Aveda salon
store or spa check the description box
for more information and I'll see you
next time
[Music]